{
    "subject": "resource/Angus_McKelvey",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Honolulu",
    "human_readable": "Angus McKelvey was born in Honolulu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9497724771499634,
            "question": "Is Angus McKelvey from Honolulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9276637434959412,
            "question": "Where was Angus McKelvey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990583181381226,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Angus McKelvey was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.712221622467041,
            "question": "Can you tell me a fact about Angus McKelvey's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6897581219673157,
            "question": "What might Angus McKelvey's upbringing be like in Honolulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776100158691406,
            "question": "Are there any famous people who were also born in Honolulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.565992534160614,
            "question": "Angus McKelvey's birthdate would tell us how old he is."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3639833629131317,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Angus McKelvey's parents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12777802348136902,
            "question": "Honolulu is known for its beautiful beaches.  Do you know anything else about Honolulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10860385745763779,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Honolulu?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Angus McKelvey was born in Honolulu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8243_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Honolulu is known for its beautiful beaches.  Do you know anything else about Honolulu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8243_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Angus McKelvey's parents?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8243_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Angus McKelvey's birthdate would tell us how old he is.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8243_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8243_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention Angus McKelvey's birthplace as Honolulu, Hawaii."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Angus L.K. McKelvey was born in 1968 in Honolulu, Hawaii,\" which supports the statement that Angus McKelvey was born in Honolulu."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}